副总统
第五季 第一集
选举翌日
上午 9:04
我亲爱的美国同胞们
My fellow Americans,
今晨我以对我们至上的民主政体
I stand before you this morning in barefaced awe
校对:苹果酒
监制:Jereau 苹果酒
压制:天天
无比敬畏之心站在你们面前
of the majesty of our democratic system.
多么神奇的夜晚
What a night.
在我们这样的民主国家
In a democracy such as ours,
靠其公民选出其总统
it falls to the people to choose their president,
这也是你们昨晚所经历的
and that is what you attempted to do last night.
而结果却是 在总统选举团中
As it turned out, there's a virtually unprecedented tie
存在前所未有的平局
in the electoral college,
许多学者都认为选举平局
a somewhat arcane institution
这样罕见晦涩的情况早该被废除
that many scholars believe we should do away with.
内华达 拉夫洛克市政厅
人口 1947
而我个人想要表达的是
I wish to say on a personal note
尽管当下存在平局
that although there is a tie,
我也十分荣幸能取得众多票数
I am most privileged to have won the popular vote.
尽管这僵局令人沮丧泄气
And though this tie may be frustrating,
我向美国人民保证
I want to assure the American people
我们国家绝不会群龙无首
our country is not leaderless.
不管你支持谁 我现在仍是你们的总统
No matter who you voted for, I am your president.
谢谢你们 上帝保佑你们
Thank you all. God bless you.
也惟愿上帝保佑美利坚合众国
And may God bless the United States of America.
结束
We're clear.
下面我们谈吧? 演讲真棒
Can we have the room? Fantastic speech, ma'am.
三个重点 坚定 稳定 还有镇定地胡说
The three Ss-- strength, stability and bullshit.
我忘记感谢选民让我们国家
Yeah, I forgot to thank the voters for
看上去像高中里的西班牙社团
making our country look like a high school Spanish club.
那些操蛋的国父们不知道什么叫奇数吗?
Didn't those founding fuckers ever hear of an odd number?
希腊社会给我们的两大贡献...
Two great Greek contributions to society...
民主还有花式操蛋
democracy and getting fucked up the ass.
这俩我还都试过 言过其实 就像爵士
I've tried both and they're way overrated, like jazz.
我保龄球教练曾说打平局就像亲了你妹一样
My bowling coach used to say a tie was like kissing your sister.
这感觉就像我妹在我胸上拉了坨屎
Well, this feels like my sister took a shit on my chest.
我天 我也告诉你啊
God, I'll tell you something, too, okay?
打死我也不要给那个骄傲自大 迪克·凡·戴克
There is no world in which I am going to be vice president
一样的操蛋汤姆·詹姆斯做副总统
to that smug, Dick Van Dyke-looking motherfucker Tom James.
见鬼了他妈的他以为是谁...
Who in the hell does he think...
凯瑟琳你拿着那东西在干吗啊?
Catherine, what are you doing with that thing?
- 开着吗? - 还记得我们做完回去的时候吗?
- Is that on? - Remember when we got back last night?
这是我的论文电影 关于这个平局
My thesis film about the tie.
她是瓦萨大学电影专业的
She majored in film at Vassar College.
相信我 我知道她学什么
Oh, believe me, I know what she majored in.
每年花六万五千刀看电影
65 grand a year to watch movies.
妈 这绝对是历史性事件
Mom, this is such a historic event.
你能行行好离我远点吗?
Can you please just get off of me?
那我永远不会弄出我导师喜欢的课题了
And I never came up with a thesis my advisor liked
因为我上半学年有过
because I had that thing
全程把我累的不要不要的...
last semester where I was tired all the time...
好的 我们没时间听你叨叨你的症状
Okay, we don't have time to hear the story of your syndrome.
你的辅修呢 舞蹈?
What about your minor, dance?
你怎么不为我这选举
Why don't you make up a
编一支舞呢?
little kind of a dance about the election?
也是课题啊 比如说你在
You know, you can't decide
你该不该跳舞中挣扎
should you dance or should you not dance?
你得严肃看待这事儿 你保证过我的
I want you to take this seriously. You promised me.
行行好 凯瑟琳 别发牢骚了 好嘛?
Please, Catherine, stop with the whining, all right?
你都快把这儿的防弹玻璃震碎了
You're gonna shatter the bulletproof glass in here.
我们没拿下特拉华州是什么鬼?
How is it that we did not win Delaware?
所以你的回答是 是?
Okay, is that a yes to my question?
好的吧 她享有完全通行权 可以吗?
Okay, she can have full access, okay?
在我们讨论完也门问题之后
Starting right after we address the situation in Yemen.
亲爱的 也门
Honey, it's Yemen.
当生活给你也门 你得榨成也门汁
Life gives you Yemen, you got to make Yemenade.
好吧 我等会再来
Okay, well, I'll come back later.
反正你也会回来的
You always do.
女士
Ma'am.
不 电影没戏
No, there's not gonna be a film.
凯瑟琳做成的唯一一件事
The only thing Catherine ever finished
就是消灭一整块冰淇淋蛋糕
was an entire ice cream cake.
也门这个借口想得快准狠 不错
Quick thinking about Yemen, by the way.
事实上 四名基督教传教士被烧至死
Actually, four Christian missionaries burned to death.
更好了
Oh, even better.
艾米! 上帝啊
Amy! Jesus.
我这边脸上的这东西感觉像是狗的乳头
This thing on the side of my face feels like a dog nipple.
很难发现的 女士
It's hardly noticeable, ma'am,
就像我们我们西班牙选民投票结果
like our Hispanic voter turnout.
我估计你得去看看医生了
Maybe you just might want to see a doctor just in case.
不 她不需要医生 一切尽在掌握
No, she doesn't need a doctor. I got it under control.
- 艾米! - 哈?
- Amy! - Yeah?
- 所以怎样? - 没啥
- So, what? - Nothing.
我整晚都在
I've been on the phone all night with these clueless
和我们这些无能的宪法律师专家通话
constitutional law experts of ours.
我都不知道怎么让他们"硬"一点
I don't know what's getting their dicks harder,
选举平局还是和一个女孩谈话
an electoral college tie or talking to a girl.
- 你回来了吗? - 不 我就是来帮个忙
- Are you back? - No, I'm not back. I'm just helping out.
- 女士 - 又咋了?
- Ma'am. - What?
你想就你那个看看医生吗...
Do you want to see a doctor about the...
- 是个压力痘痘 - 不 它是
- It's a stress pimple. - No, it's
- 我屁股上老长 - 不是压力痘痘
- I get them on my ass all the time. - It's not a stress pimple.
只是一个普通痘痘长在了压力比较大的时候
It's a pimple that erupted during a very stressful time.
- 盖瑞已经在处理了 好嘛? - 绝对 好
- Gary's on it, okay? - Exactly, yes.
- 我没有勺子 - 啊
- I don't have a spoon. - Oh.
你试过苹果醋吗?
Have you tried cider vinegar?
没 我们用热敷就够了
No, we're using hot compresses. That's all we need.
治压力疙瘩? 本屁股上也有
For the stress pimple? Ben
她得看医生了
gets those on his butt. She should see a doctor.
- 艾米回来了 - 不 我还没回
- Amy's back. - No, I'm not back.
- 演讲的反响棒呆了 - 好
- Ma'am, rave reviews on the speech. - Good.
- 还有个大新闻 - 上帝啊 奥布莱恩陈词了?
- Oh, and big news. - Oh, God, O'Brien made a statement?
对不起 我应该说这是私人大新闻的
I'm sorry, I should have said big personal news.
温蒂和我要从中国领养一个宝宝啦
Wendy and I are adopting a baby from China.
我们原本准备在选举之后再公布的
We were keeping it a secret till after the election.
好吧说实话 温蒂也才是今天刚刚告诉我
Actually, Wendy was keeping it a secret from me until today
因为我藏不住秘密
because I'm so bad with keeping secrets.
- 但我要晋升为人父啦 - 你就一傻逼
- But I'm gonna be a dad. - You're a nincompoop.
我们处在选举平局的中艰阶段
We are in the middle of a tied election.
可没啥时间给什么中国宝宝
There is no time for some Chinese baby.
宝宝退了吧 看你能不能把钱要回来
Cancel it and see if you can get your money back.
幸运的曲奇说你搞砸了 小圆眼
Fortune cookie say you fuck up big-time, round eye.
没啥大不了 我都不知道宝宝什么时候回来
It's not a big deal. I don't even know when to expect her.
今天开始 我得练就一身父亲的体形了
And, starting today, I'm getting in dad shape.
- 数我的步伐 - 真可惜你没细数你失足的步伐
- Counting my steps. - Too bad you're not counting your missteps.
你早餐时就可以解决了 是吧?
You'd be done by breakfast, right?
我还是喜欢在脑海中数
I prefer to count my steps in my head.
4383步
4,383.
滚出我视野 肯特 好嘛?
Get out of my sight, Kent, okay?
就这破平局我还没原谅你呢
I have not forgiven you for this tie.
女士 我这有众议院最终的结果
Ma'am, I have the final House results.
- 拉封丹赢了? - 嗯
- Lafontaine won? - Mm-hmm.
一个反对堕胎的人得让他的
How many abortions does a pro-lifer
情妇堕胎几次才能让人们都去痛恨他?
have to pressure his mistress into before the people turn on him?
- 3次 - 克雷格是怎么输的?
- Three. - And how did Craig lose?
她不是去过印第安纳州五次吗?
Didn't she go to Indiana, like, five times?
那估计就是问题所在了
That may have been the problem.
好的吧 听着 从现在开始
All right, listen. From this moment forward,
众议院拉票是关键
people, I am all about the House vote.
我们建议单独约
We are recommending direct
国会议员见面
engagement with individual congressmen.
- 就这么说定了 - 就这样
- That's got to happen. - That's right.
而且每天你们都得做奥布莱恩做不了的事
And every day you have to do the one thing O'Brien can't do.
- 对 像是不喝酒开车 - 还有拉屎时没有疝气
- Yeah, drive sober. - Take a shit without getting a hernia.
是做个总统 当务之急是
Be the president. It is imperative
你得看上去像个总统
that you look presidential right now.
我要去拜访军队
I'm going to visit troops,
上下空军一号越多越好
go on and off of Air Force One as much as possible.
- 我们都不必离开地面 - 对
- We don't even have to leave the ground. - Right.
女士 你可能得考虑
Ma'am, you may want to consider
举办那个关于种族的研讨会了
moving up that symposium on race.
我并不觉得我们得这么快开那个操蛋的研讨会
I don't think that we're symposium on race desperate yet.
- 懂我的意思? - 嗨
- All right? - Hi.
不好意思我迟了
Sorry I'm late.
太奇怪了 我竟然同意艾米刚刚说的每句话
Strangely, I agree with everything Amy just said.
我也推荐
And if I may also suggest
重新利用选举的推特账户
repurposing the election Twitter account
创建一个总统账户和美国群众直接对话
to a new POTUS account to talk directly to the American people.
好主意 比尔 你能不能...
Great idea, Bill. Could you...
你能不能暂时先出去下?
could you step outside for a moment, please?
好
Sure.
能比你出现在罗斯福房间
There's only one person
更让我惊讶的就只有他妈的泰迪·罗斯福
I'd be more surprised to see today in the Roosevelt Room
自己的鬼魂出现在这了 你来干嘛
and that's Teddy fucking Roosevelt.
我只是想帮帮总统
I'm just trying to help the president.
她心领了
And she appreciates that.
但是哥伦比亚特区的检察长
But the US Attorney for the
正准备起诉你
District of Columbia is prepared to indict you.
你在这的受欢迎程度就像在犹太人教堂里的一坨纳粹形状的屎
You're as welcome here as a swastika-shaped shit in a synagogue.
- 当然 - 我和总统谈过
- Of course. - I spoke with the president
她愿意考虑完全的原谅
and she's willing to reconsider a full pardon
如果你悄悄投降 没有媒体报道
if you surrender quietly. No media.
只是别想支配新闻圈
Just don't want to dominate the news cycle.
- 我能说件事吗? - 好嘞 再见
- Can I just say one thing? - Yes, good-bye.
所以 这事咋样?
So, how'd it go?
他像一个男人一样接受了
He took it like a man.
哇 他最好习惯 啐
Oh, well, he better get used to that. Pfft.
她多可爱呀?
Isn't she adorable?
- 我看他们都长一样 - 什么?
- Oh, they all look alike to me. - What?
不是中国人 是小孩的图片 多大了?
Not Chinese people, but pictures of children. How old?
中介说她要么十六个月要么三岁
The agency says she's either 16 months or three years old.
- 你喜欢你的健康腕带吗? - 当然
- Do you like your Fitbit? - Oh, yeah.
对 我今天已经超过一万两千步了呢
I am just over 12,000 steps today.
我只有三千 你跑来上班的嘛?
I'm at 3,000. Did you run to work today?
不 工作让我一直活跃着
No, the job keeps me active.
总统办公室
Office of the president.
请稍等
Hold, please.
稍后回来的是 民意调查员事后析误
When we come back, the pollster postmortem.
总统选举打平 载入史书
为什么出口民调如此差强人意?
Why were the exit polls so off?
- 喔 格雷格 - 丹
- Oh, Greg. Greg. - Dan.
- 昨晚干得漂亮 - 谢谢
- Great job last night. - Thank you.
我看见 马蒂·柯蒂斯 在停车场哭了
I saw Matty Curtis crying in the parking garage.
不可思议 嘿
That's fantastic. Hey, listen.
我很期待能重新回来 但是他们一直让我等着
I was really hoping to get back on, but they got me waiting
- 在休息室 大概两个小时了 - 斯博迪来了
- in the greenroom for, like, two hours. - Spauldy showed up.
他在这了 他正在做头发 还是回家吧 我觉得
He's here. He's getting his hair done. Just go home, I guess.
但是我昨晚上通杀了呀 对不对?
But I killed it last night, right?
丹 我觉得你在这会有不错的发展
Dan, look, I think you could have a future in this,
但是你必须走出去给自己赚点名气
but you got to get out there and make a name for yourself.
你负责了两周的竞选 然后精神崩溃了
You ran one campaign for two weeks and had a nervous breakdown.
医学上这么说是不准确的
That is medically inaccurate.
出去赢个信基督恐同的同性恋
Go out, win a race with a Jesus-loving
或者是什么种族歧视的亿万富翁
homophobic homosexual or a racist billionaire.
然后我们再来说说你的职业生涯
Then we can talk about a career in TV.
- 痘巨人看起来怎么样? - 生气 你挤它了吗?
- How's Zitzilla looking? - Angry. You been picking at it?
没有
No.
稍微挤了一下 但是...
Ahem, well, maybe a little bit, but...
- 哇! 天呐 - 上帝啊 怎么了? 怎么了?
- Ow! Oh, my God. - Oh, my God. What? What?
- 操这也太热了 - 本来就应该热的
- Oh, that is so hot. - It's supposed to be hot.
而且茶是凉的
And the tea is cold.
总统女士 今晨
Madam President, Chinese hackers
中国的黑客们突破了国家安全局的防火墙
breached an NSA firewall earlier this morning.
- 黑客有没有顺手修好WiFi? - 我查一下
- Any chance they fixed the Wi-Fi? - I'll check.
联邦情报局的负责人正在等着见你
And the director of the Secret Service is waiting to see you.
让他进来 如果他在等着见我 还能怎样...
Then send him in. If he's been waiting to see me, I mean...
- 嗨 基斯 - 很抱歉打扰你 女士
- Hi, Keith. - Sorry to bother you, ma'am.
没有 谈不上打扰
No, it's okay. It's no bother.
自从你成为了总统 我们一直在
Since you became president, we have
寻找一个新的领头特工负责你的安保细节
been looking for a new lead agent for your detail.
我挺喜欢鲍勃的啊 除了那颗褪色的牙
Gosh, I like Bob. I mean, apart from the discolored tooth.
但这明显不是一个换掉他的理由啊
But that's obviously not a reason to replace him.
- 他们能把那颗牙换掉吗? -不能
- Can they replace the tooth? - No, no.
女士 这位是特殊探员 马乔里·帕尔苗蒂
Ma'am, this is Special Agent Marjorie Palmiotti.
- 你好 - 你好 女士
- Oh, hello. - Hello, ma'am.
- 是探员? - 帕尔苗蒂
- Agent? - Palmiotti.
- 帕尔苗蒂 欢迎加入 - 谢谢您
- Palmiotti, okay. Welcome aboard. - Thank you.
女士 成为领头特工的一个关键要素就是
Ma'am, a key requirement for being lead agent
要看起来像总统 尤其是从背后看起来
is someone who looks like the president, especially from behind,
向任何潜在刺客提供
to provide an additional
多一个可能的诱饵
decoy target for any would-be assailants.
我完美的匹配你的背影
I'm a perfect match from behind.
好的 我要告诉你
Um, okay, I'll tell you something.
我没太看出来
I am not quite seeing it,
只因为我很…
um, only because I'm...
然而 你...
well, you are...
- 女士? - 就是... 你介不介意给我们一点时间
- Ma'am? - It's just... would you mind just giving us a second,
特工 帕尔... 谢谢你
Agent Palmi... thank you.
基斯 你真的看不出来吗?
Keith, are you really not seeing what it is I'm seeing?
- 看不出来 女士  - 盖瑞 你来说?
- No, ma'am. - Gary, can you help me out here?
她闻起来完全不一样 所以 你懂得...
She smells completely different, so, you know...
我不是说这个... 不是...
That is not what... t's not...
不好意思 女士 如果你... 对不起
Excuse me, ma'am, if you... I’m sorry.
- 什么? - 你必须看看这个 女士
- What? - You've got to see this, ma'am.
- 很高兴见到你   - 很高兴见到你  女士
- Pleasure to meet you. - Pleasure to meet you, ma'am.
我去
Oh, shit.
此刻的重大新闻... 内华达州
The big story at this moment... Nevada.
所有的选票已经记录
With all the votes now tallied,
总统选举团全部打平
总统职位待定
议员比尔·奥布莱恩赶超了总统赛琳娜·梅耶
Senator Bill O'Brien's lead over President Selina Meyer
不足百分之零点五 根据内华达州法律
is now less than half a percent, which by Nevada state law
重新计数极其有可能发生
would allow for a possible recount.
内华达重算或让梅耶当选
如果总统梅耶 可以在重新投票中胜出
If President Meyer were to win a recount,
她就会赢得内华达的六次投票选举
she wins Nevada's six electoral votes
也就赢得了总统席位
and therefore the presidency.
- 所有的网站都在说这个  - 《纽约时报》也是
- All the networks have it. - "New York Times" As well.
天呐! 哦 等一下
Oh, my God! Oh, wait.
大家字幕组
EVERYONE
m 16 2 l 3 8 l 12 8 l 12 6 l 16 6 m 33 -5 l 37 8 l 42 8 m 29 -12 l 21 -12 l 24 -10 l 24 6 l 23 8 l 30 8 l 25 -5 l 27 -10 l 31 -10 m -15 -5 l -23 8 l -7 8 m -9 -12 l 12 -12 l 2 -8 l 2 -4 l 13 -9 l 15 -7 l 2 -1 l 2 2 l 16 -4 l 16 -2 l 2 4 l 1 6 m -11 -24 l 15 -24 l 15 -22 l 1 -22 l 1 -16 l 11 -16 l 11 -19 l 25 -19 l 28 -15 l -11 -15 m -20 -22 l -24 -15 l -20 -15 m -26 -12 l -21 -12 l -32 6 l -33 6 l -33 8 l -39 8
大家字幕组
等一下 等一下
Wait a minute, wait a minute,
等一下 这是真的吗?
wait a minute. Is this really happening?
我是说 我们真的在内花达重新有一次机会?
I mean, do we actually have a chance at Nevada?
- 是内华达 - 天呐
- "Nev-add-a." - Oh, my God.
我可以当总统啦 我不用搬家啦 我们要做什么?
I get to be president. I don't have to move. What do we do?
大家字幕组
女士 我们需要百分百确定当我们到了...
Ma'am, we need to be sure that when we get on…
不 闭嘴肯特 你已经让我在内花达输过一次了
No, shut up, Kent. You already lost Nevada for me once.
- "内华达." - 本我们要怎么做?
- "Nev-add-a." - Ben, what do we do?
我们需要稳住那些内华达已有的支持者 别 别
Uh, we need to get ahold of our people in Nevada. Don't. Don't.
大部分内华达的投票是通过机器
The vast majority of Nevada voting is done by machine.
一旦内华达的州政府公证了那些投票
Once the Nevada Secretary of State certifies the count,
我们就会有72个小时来申请一个重新计数
we'll then have 72 hours to request a recount.
在那个时候 会选出5%的范围
At that point, 5% of the precincts will be selected,
如果此范围的误差高于1%
and if there's a discrepancy of more than 1%,
就可以申请一个全面的重新投票
a full hand recount will be requested.
我的博士学位研究的就是在西部的重新计数选举程序
I actually did my doctorate in recount procedures in the West.
一级棒理查德 理查德现在为我工作
Excellent work, Richard. Richard works for me.
- 你有个博士学位? - 两个
- You have a doctorate? - Two.
宪法和兽医
Constitutional law and veterinary medicine,
- 这是我的后备计划 - 但你之前是给我倒咖啡的
- which was my fallback. - But you were getting my coffee.
这个更难 因为你有很多不同的心情
Which is much harder 'cause you have so many different moods.
比如一半咖啡和全杯咖啡 黑糖玛基朵
Like a half-caff and a full-caff, macchiato.
- "玛奇朵." - 玛奇朵
- "Ma-key-ato." - Macchiato.
好啦 理查德 你来做我的重数特派员
Okay, Richard, you are going to be my recount specialist.
- 乔纳 你为理查德工作 - 等一下 什么?
- Jonah, you're working for Richard. - Wait, what?
艾米 你把这些事情都理个清楚 好吗?
Amy, you got to sort all of this out, okay?
女士 我不能去内华达 我都不能说我真在这里
Ma'am, I really can't go to Nevada. I'm not even really here.
女士 奥布莱恩要在一个小时内
Ma'am, O'Brien is calling a
举办一场新闻发布会讨论关于重新计数的事情
press conference in an hour to discuss the recount.
我会在半小时内发表讲话 好吗?
I'm gonna talk in a half an hour, okay?
我要在他说屁话之前先说话
I got to say stuff before he says stuff.
- 听着 你要去写点什么 - 我现在就去
- Listen, you got to write something up. - I'm on it.
马上 重数 重数
Right now. Ooh, recount, recount.
乔纳 跟着我 谢谢
Jonah, with me, please.
这简直是超级无敌大狗屎
This is highly enriched weapons-grade bullshit.
她怎么敢让你领导我?
How dare she put you in charge of me?
这就是货真价实的暴行
It's an outrage is what it is.
这就是暴行 你知道吗?
It is an outrage, you know?
她就像是 德斯礼舅舅 然后她有一个
She's Uncle Dursley and she's got
厉害的哈利波特藏在楼梯里
the great wizard Harry Potter living under the staircase.
你看到了吗? 但是哈利波特书里到底发生了什么?
Do you see that? But what happens in the Harry Potter books?
他崛起了然后杀了所有的麻瓜
He rises up and he kills all the muggles.
不是这样的
I don't think that's what happens.
事实上 很抱歉 那个腰撑是这个椅子的
Actually, I'm sorry, that lumbar support goes with this chair.
- 对 我们马上就到 - 好的 你写了什么?
- Yeah, we're getting there. - Okay, so what do you got?
我是否仍然厚颜无耻的
Am I still standing in barefaced
敬畏着我们的民主制度?
awe of the majesty of our democratic system?
- 不完全 女士 这次
- Not exactly, ma'am. This time
- 抱歉 - 什么?
- Oh, sorry. - What?
成功走满5000步的提醒
Just hit 5,000 steps on my Fitbit.
- 好吧 好吧 - 这次 你就是简单地备受眷顾
- Okay, okay. - This time, you're simply blessed.
哇 我还以为你的上一篇是华丽空洞的废话呢
Wow, I thought your last one was flowery, vacuous nonsense.
这一个更糟了 做得好 迈克
This one is much worse. Excellent, Mike.
盖瑞 盖个痘痘的时间我都能
Gary, this is taking longer than it did
- 装修完一栋房子了 - 我们必须走起了
- for them to paint my fucking pool house. - We got to go.
- 下午好 - 下午好
- Good afternoon. - Good afternoon.
人满为患啊
Yes, oh, wow. Look at this full house.
当我想到我们伟大的国家的时候
When I think about this great country of ours,
我不得不细数我的幸运
I have to count my blessings.
今日早些 正如你们记得的那样
Earlier today as you'll remember,
梅耶总统第二次发表全国性讲话
我对于事态的发展做了简短的报告...
I briefed you on the state of affairs regarding...
看起来更糟了
It's looking a little worse.
不管你站在这个屋子的哪里
Wherever you stand in the room,
它都一直盯着你
it's still looking at you.
从那时起 我们在内华达新发展就像是
Since that time, we have been doubly blessed
被双倍的眷顾了
by new developments in the state of Nevada.
而且我很自信...
And I am confident...
- ...所有的美国民众
- ...that all Americans,
包括奥布莱恩议员...
including Senator O'Brien...
- 别管它 别管它 - 加油
- Leave it. Leave it. - Come on.
这是我作为总统义不容辞的义务
It is my clear duty as president
来加强贯彻这个国家的法律
to enforce the laws of this country
在小心评估了
after a careful assessment
各项法律真正的意义的前提下
of what those laws actually mean.
- 能成为你们的总统候选人是我的幸运
- I am also blessed to be your candidate for president.
- 这是什么? - 痘痘破了? 破了吗?
- What is this? - Did it pop? Did it pop?
道琼斯指数比我夏天的蛋蛋还要低
The Dow is dropping lower than my balls on a hot summer day.
因选举不确定性 股票大量抛售
尽管美国人民有些时候会...
While the American people may sometimes be...
都是那个该死的痘痘
It's the fucking pimple.
痘巨人刚刚卷席了华尔街
Zitzilla just stomped all over Wall Street.
于此而言  我们都是被祝福的
And in that, we are all blessed.
谢谢你们
Thank you.
那么 怎么样?
So, how was that?
道琼斯指数下降了986...
The Dow has dropped 986...
日你妹啊
Oh, suck my dick.
二次计票造成的恐慌导致了证券大跌
Panic from the recount led to a huge sell-off
市场已经被过度下注了
and the market is so overmargined, blammo.
道琼斯指数自2008年以来降到最低
他们已经开始说是黑色星期三了
They're already calling it Black Wednesday.
天呐 今天才星期三吗?
Jesus, it's only Wednesday?
而且奥布莱恩 刚刚发布了一项声明
And O'Brien just issued a statement.
他说 "市场的崩溃
He says, "The market crash
是美国的脸上的一个污点"
caused a blotch on the face of America."
那说我的痘痘吗?
Is that about my pimple?
周二选举被华尔街黑色星期三盖过风头
反正痘痘也没帮啥忙
Well, I don't think it helped.
- 盖瑞  - 嗯?
- Gary. - Yeah?
- 我想要看医生 -好的 我只是觉得没必要...
- I want to see a doctor. - Okay, I just don't think...
是你造成的 那些热敷让它长更大了
You did this, okay? All that heat made it grow bigger.
你在我脸上烤了个舒芙蕾饼
You baked a fucking souffle on my face.
总统阁下 一切痘好吗?
Madam President. Howzit going?
他是不是刚说了 痘?
Did he just say zit?
为什么从没有人暗杀过副总统呢?
How come no one ever tries to assassinate a vice president?
接下来 我们要在经济方面采取什么举措?
Okay, so what are we going to do about the economy?
我们何不从任命一位经济专家开始呢?
Why don't we appoint an economy
至少像那么回事
czar for a start? That seems like something.
就好比把一辆空的警车停在
Like an empty cop car they
马路对面 让来往的司机都减减速那样子
park on the side of the road to slow speeders.
那些警车里都没人?
Those cars are empty?
- 行了 你给我坐下 - 是的 夫人
- Okay, you've got to sit down. - Yes, ma'am.
同志们 是时候把种族研讨会提上议程了
Guys, it might be time to move up the symposium on race.
我在跟进了 夫人 兢兢业业的
I'm on it, ma'am, like brown on rice.
夫人 汤姆·詹姆斯刚在该死的
Ma'am, Tom James just gave
《坦荡君子》上接受了采访
an interview to the Bumfuck "Plain Dealer"
我引用一下他的原话
where he says, and I quote,
"我只想确认一下他们是否在重算
"I just want to make sure they're recounting
所有海外现役军人的
all the absentee ballots of
缺席选票"
our men and women bravely serving overseas."
- 联合通讯社也是这么写的 - 他在干嘛?
- It's up on AP, too. - What is he doing?
他明明知道军队不待见我
He knows that the military hates me.
反正肯定会给奥布莱恩拉来更多选票
There are only bound to be more votes for O'Brien.
而我们需要你的票多点 他的票少点 女士
We need less of those and more votes for you, ma'am.
有道理啊?
You think?
错了 我们要做的是给他们敲一遍警钟
No, what we have to do is hang a bell on this guy.
他太不按规矩来了
He's completely off book.
不是的 夫人 我觉得他只是在熟悉他的台词而已
No, ma'am, I think that means that he's learned all his lines
都快滚瓜烂熟了
and he no longer needs a script.
- 不 他的行为出轨了 - 出柜?
- No, he's off book. - Off the hook?
不是 他... 天 他讲的话偏离了
No, he's... God, he's deviating from the book
原本的轨道
of the things that he should do.
- 噢你说脱轨了 - 噢
- You mean off the rails. - Oh.
好吧 他的行为脱轨了
Fine, he's off the rails.
那么 让汤姆来当经济专家好了
Well, let's make Tom economy czar.
可以有
Yeah.
我们让他专门干这活 这会让他忙疯的
We'll czar him. That'll give him something to do.
好 我们就从这个开始
All right, we're gonna start with that.
艾米 我想跟你谈谈
Amy, Amy, I just need to talk to you for one second.
我有个很严肃的问题
I've got a very big question.
我不能去内华达 我很抱歉
I can't go to Nevada. I'm sorry.
我考虑这个问题考虑了很久 真的
I have thought about this a lot.
你觉得凯蒂·卡罗索
What do you think of Candi Caruso
帮我管理内华达事务怎么样?
to head up Nevada for me?
好啊
Oh, yeah.
我听说她相当能干
I hear just excellent things about her.
- 负责过哈佛法律周刊 - 没错
- "Harvard Law Review." - Right.
她给坦尼法官当过书记员
She clerked for Justice Tenny.
- 30岁以下的30个最佳政客 - 是的
- "Politico"'s 30 under 30. - That's right.
她现在还不到30岁 她看起来显老 但是...
She's still under 30. She looks older, but...
- 你觉得她不错吧? - 当然
- You like her? Yeah. - Yes.
我的意思是 如果你需要一个超级能干
I mean, if you want a super smart woman
还年轻貌美睿智无比的女人 那干嘛不选她?
who's young and brilliant, then why not?
对啊 我就是这么想的
Yeah, I really want that.
真的
I really do.
听着 除去那些重新核对的选票
Look, regardless of the recount,
西德尼·珀塞尔办公室
下午 1:20
这对小西葫芦来说还是一件大喜事
this could mean big things for zucchini.
嗯 好 我们迟点再说 拜
Yeah, good. We'll talk later. Bye.
丹尼男孩 昨晚在电视上看到你了
Hey, Danny boy. Saw you on TV last night.
- 讲得不错 - 不敢当啊
- Nicely done. - Yeah. Thank you.
不过我的确想跟你说这档子事
That's actually what I wanted to talk to you about.
- 说吧 - 你看 我需要做些改变
- Uh-huh. - See, I need to make some changes.
可以等我一小小会吗?
Can you just let me hold on one quick second?
- 可以 - 等我发完这条短信 好了 请继续
- Yeah. - Shoot off this text. Sorry, go ahead.
- 你刚刚在讲吗? - 是的
- You were saying? - I was.
我在说我十分享受在这里的每分每秒
I was saying that I really enjoyed my time here.
- 噢 是吗 - 我也从你这里学到了很多
- Oh, good. - And I've learned so much from you.
我十分荣幸
That's good to hear.
- 不好意思 - 没事 看吧
- Sorry about that. - Go ahead, take that.
- 真的? - 对啊
- Yeah? - Yeah.
- 你发来的? - 是吗?
- It's from you? - Is it?
- 我被炒了? - 对的 请出去
- I'm fired? - Yes, get out.
我们给奥布莱恩加注了大筹码
We are doubling down on O'Brien,
所以你现在跟路边40岁大妈一样没用
so you're basically as useless to me as a 40-year-old woman.
好吧 那...
Okay, well...
有意思啊 收到了你的短信呢
Oh, interesting. Getting something back from you.
噢 "你才没有炒掉我 是我要退粗的"
Oh, "You can't fire me, I quib."
我本来想打退出的
You know it's supposed to say quit.
我就是炒你鱿鱼怎么着 你才不能退粗 你个二洒子
Well, I just fired you anyway. You can't quib, you rebard.
白宫
上午 9:11
夫人 有人给你脸上的痘痘开了个推特账号
Ma'am, someone opened a Twitter account for the pimple.
- 啥? - 叫POTUS
- What? - It's called POTUS.
- 美利坚合众国的小疙瘩 - 好吧
- Pimple of the United States. - Okay.
五分钟之前刷新的 粉丝都过20万了
There are 220,000 followers as of five minutes ago.
我推特上的粉丝有多少?
How many Twitter followers do I have?
接近那个数
Approaching that.
现在还有什么不那么操蛋的消息要告诉我吗?
Is there anything not fucked up that you can tell me right now?
种族研讨会场已经布置好了 下午就开
Well, the symposium on race is all set for this afternoon.
挺好的 看吧 种族平等的号角就要吹响
Oh, good. Well, that'll be a hoot.
噢 我们的经济大家来了 借过一下 先生
Oh, czar she blows. Excuse me, gentlemen.
...周日跟媒体解释
...with the press on Sundays.
- 嗨 汤姆打扰了 - 总统夫人
- Hey, Tom. Excuse me. - Madam President.
- 你还好吗? - 不错
- How are you? - I am good.
- 你了解内华达的最新情况吗? - 是啊
- So you're up to speed on Nevada? - Uh-huh.
- 现在的市场状况呢 - 我也看到了
- And the markets now. - I saw that.
天哪 这也是我要说的
My God. Which brings me to my point.
- 我想正式地任命你... - 不不不
- Um, I would like to officially offer you... - No, no, no, no.
- ...当白宫的经济专家 - 别别别
- ...the position of economy czar. - Nope, nope, nope.
十分感谢 但请允许我拒绝
Thank you, but no.
为什么呢? 你可以接手处理经济危机了
Why not? You would be in charge of the economic crisis.
不 我会因经济危机而受到责难的
No, I would be blamed for the economic crisis.
汤姆 得了吧 你想当财政部长
Tom, stop it. You wanted to be Treasury Secretary.
不记得了吗? 我不觉得这跟财政部长有什么不同
Remember? I don't see how this is any different than that.
恕我直言 总统夫人 我希望您能分清两者
Well, respectfully, Madam President, I hope you do
如果连美国总统
because if the President of the United States
都不能区分财政部长跟
can't tell the difference between Treasury Secretary
管证券市场的受气包 那就很尴尬了
and stock market patsy, that's pretty disturbing.
那你接受吗?
Then you accept?
总统夫人 我十分荣幸
Madam President, it is a huge honor,
但我必须权衡自己的所想所作所为 我敬谢不敏
but I have to balance that against my need not to do it.
汤姆 我在以美利坚合众国
Tom, I'm asking you
总统的身份请求你
as the President of the United States.
而我 毕恭毕敬地 拒绝
And, respectfully, I am declining.
我并没感觉到尊敬啊
I'm not picking up any respect.
但是感觉到我拒绝了吧?
But you're getting the declining?
你知道凯蒂·卡罗索的真名是什么吗?
Do you know what Candi Caruso's real name is?
是坎迪斯 她把名字改成了糖果 只不过后面是I而已
It's Candice. And she changed it to Candi with an I.
如果她都能把自己名字改成这鬼样
If she does that to her own goddamn name,
谁能担保她把那些重新计算的选票改成什么样?
how the hell is she going to handle a potential recount?
早上好 艾米 这是总统的日程表
Good morning, Amy. This is the president's schedule,
并且 顺便说一句 卡罗索已经上任了
which, incidentally, Ms. Caruso is on right now.
- 对 我明白 - 早上好 夫人
- Oh, I'm aware. - Oh, good morning, ma'am.
- 早上好 - 夫人...
- Good morning. - Hey, ma'am...
我看到了 请你离我的脸蛋远远的
Okay, I see you. You stay away from my face.
我听到了 但这是我萨凡纳阿姨家的食谱
I hear you, but this is a family recipe from my aunts in Savannah
他们坚称能根治皮肤病跟偏头痛
and they swear by it for skin problems and migraines.
- 然后呢 - 鹰嘴豆作底料 加点塔巴斯科辣酱油 搅拌...
- Mm-hmm. - Chickpea based, Tabasco, with just a dash...
你这样说让我觉得很饿
All you're doing right now is making me hungry.
- 所以你为什么不给我拿点吃的? - 好好好
- So why don't you do something about that? - Sure, sure.
- 零食 - 对啊
- Snack. - Uh-huh, yeah.
艾米 你想跟我说什么吗?
Amy, did you need me for anything?
- 没有 我就在这待一会 - 没有? 那好
- No. I'm just chilling. - No? Mmm.
我觉得最重要的战略是
I think the most important thing in terms of strategy
掌握好你的叙述方式
is controlling the narrative.
对哦 我有句话是这么说来着 解释你就输了
Oh, I have a saying. If you're explaining, you're losing.
正是这样 我十分同意你的说法
Absolutely. I'm right on board with you.
- 打扰一席 总统女士 - 艾米
- Excuse me, Madam President. - Amy.
你见过凯蒂了吗?
Have... have you met Candi?
嗨 我是I字结尾的Candi
Hi, it's Candi with an I.
我是Y字结尾的Amy 这才是正确的拼法
Amy with a Y. Which is correct.
我们正在对
We are right in the middle of an interview
一位异常
with an exceptionally
出色的内华达州长候选人进行面试
wonderful candidate for coordinating Nevada.
夫人 这只需要耽误您很少时间
Ma'am, it's just gonna take a second.
- 不好意思 我稍后就回来 - 没事
- Apologies. I'll be right back. - Absolutely.
- 给你带了零食 - 好的 给我吧
- I got you a snack. - Oh, yeah, give me that.
裙子很漂亮
That's a great dress.
谢谢你的赞美
Oh, thank you.
二码的?
Size two?
卡罗索女士 总统夫人表示非常抱歉
Ms. Caruso, the president sends her apologies,
您竞选的职位已不再空缺
but the position has been filled.
您请
Right this way.
好吧
Okay.
如果我还需要别的衣服 到时候就叫您或妈妈寄给我
And if I need more clothes, then I'll have you or Mom send them.
好的 再见 理查德
Yeah, fine, bye. Richard.
- 这是什么? - 你认识乔纳 他是来给我干活的
- What's this? - You know Jonah. He works for me.
事实上 你们俩约会过 但是你放不下他
In fact, you two used to date, but you never got over him.
不是乔纳 为什么这个带胡子的大宝宝会在这儿?
Not Jonah. Why is baby with a beard here?
噢 你该记住克里夫了 他现在为我干活
Oh, good, you remember Cliff. He works for me now.
我把他从法院那边招过来了
I recruited him from Justice.
这是我指派众多任务的第一步
The first of many appointments I intend to make.
理查德我们得重新统计每个区的律师数量
Here, Richard, we need recount lawyers in each county
我们也得给志愿者们提供住宿
and we need housing for all the volunteers.
你能做好吗 乔纳?
Could you take care of this, Jonah?
克里夫 我现在忙得跟个陀螺一样
Cliff, my plate is just full of
我希望你能帮我搞定一下
shit right now and I'd like for you to clean that.
好吧 我来干吧 对
You know what? I'll do it. Yeah.
- 我还是很喜欢跟人谈话的 - 出去
- I love talking to people anyway. - Get out.
都走 把垫子也带上 太臭了
Out. Take that cushion with you. That is disgusting.
其实 跟座位是连在一块儿的 所以它最好还是呆着吧
Actually, it goes with the seat, so it should probably stay.
国家儿童医疗中心
上午 10:30
总统女士!
Madam President!
我怎么一个字也听不懂
I can't understand a word.
今天下午我问了汤姆·詹姆斯
This afternoon I asked Tom James
任职经济重臣
to serve as economy czar
他也同意了
and to my delight, he said yes.
总统女士!
Madam President!
詹姆斯议员的无私对我们都是一种鼓舞
Senator James' selflessness is an inspiration to us all.
无论你正在做什么无用的 徒劳的
Whatever useless, vain,
蠢事 都停下来
vapid thing you're doing right now, drop it.
我在品尝美味的三明治
Well, I am enjoying a delicious sandwich
还有个流浪汉看着我吃
made even more delicious by the
感觉更加好吃了呢
fact that there's a homeless guy watching me eat it.
我需要你陪我飞内华达州一趟
I need you to get on this plane to Nevada with me today.
去过那儿 操蛋地方
Been there, got fucked by that.
别废话了 你刚被解雇了吧
Cut the shit. You just got fired.
- 珀塞尔已经昭告天下了 – 那个混蛋!
- Purcell's told everyone in town. - That fucker!
现在你就像切尔诺贝利小便池里的蛋糕一样毒气熏天
Right now you're about as toxic as a urinal cake in Chernobyl
我这是给你提供工作
and I am offering you a job.
你有什么时间犹豫啊
You have exactly zero seconds to decide.
凯蒂·卡罗索会更友好地问我的
You know, Candi Caruso would have asked me nicer.
苏 这是总统研讨会的讲稿
Sue, the president's remarks for the symposium.
还有... 超过你了
And... caught you.
18,000步 我已经准备好迎接中国宝宝了
18,000 steps. I am Chinese baby ready.
天啊 迈克 什么时候试镜《音乐人》啊?
Oh, my God. Mike, when are the auditions for "Music Man"?
那爬了多少梯呢 迈克?
So how many flights, Mike?
- 什么梯? - 就是爬了多少层楼梯
- What do you mean flights? - As in flights of stairs.
能燃烧更多卡路里哦 我今天爬了22个
Burns way more calories. I am at 22 flights today.
什么... 楼梯?
How... stairs?
就是你走上走下的东西
The things you walk up and down.
嗨 苏 她忙吗?
Hi, Sue. Is she busy?
别管了
Oh, wow, never mind.
- 看呀 看呀 – 你怎么能这样?
- Oh, looky, looky. - How could you do this?
- 什么? - 我拒绝你了
- What? - I gave you my decision.
- 去你的 - 什么?
- Oh, suck it. - Excuse me?
你听到了 我林登·贝恩斯·约翰逊你了 好吗?
Yeah, you heard me. I LBJ'd you, okay?
我是林登·贝恩斯·约翰逊女王
I'm the LBJ queen
你就是萨金特·去你的·施赖弗
and you are Sargent "Suck It" Shriver.
不好意思我得走开一下
And now you have to excuse me,
因为这个痘痘一点都没有变小
because this pimple isn't getting any smaller.
有点像国家债务一样
Kind of like the national debt.
嘿苏 安布雷斯医生到了吗?
Hey, Sue, is Dr. Abernethy here?
- 到了 - 那好 让他进来吧
- Yes. - Okay, send him in, please.
- 你介意吗? 你好 医生 - 总统女士
- Do you mind? Hi there, Doctor. - Madam President.
你认识的詹姆斯议员 他是我们的新任经济重臣
You know Senator James. He's our new economy czar.
- 恭喜你 先生 – 谢谢
- Oh, congratulations, sir. - Thank you.
繁荣就要到了
Prosperity is just around the corner.
- 好 好 好 - 有什么能帮您的吗?
- Oh, good. Good, good. - How may I help you?
你可以帮我去除嵌在脸上的小木柱
Well, you can get rid of this Skittle that's embedded in my face.
她还有个黑痣 在紧身衣内衬里 没露出来
She's also got a mole near her Spanx line and it's hidden
紧跟在我屁股里的这人也得切除一下
Yeah, and this thing up my ass has got to get removed, too.
- 你好吗 盖瑞? - 很好 你呢?
- How are you, Gary? - Fine. You?
- 噢 埋得很深啊 - 是吧?
- Oh, yeah. That is really deep. - See?
你们都做了什么啊?
What have you been doing?
- 就是热敷了一下 – 非常烫
- Just putting heat on it. - Well, hot heat.
这事最不能做的事
That's the last thing you want to be doing.
- 好 - 没那么烫
- Okay. - It wasn't that hot.
注射一小剂可的松应该就没事儿了
Small cortisone shot should take care of it.
- 打扰一下 女士 - 进来吧
- Uh, excuse me, ma'am. - Oh, yeah, come in.
需要您过目一下研讨会的开场词
We have to go over your opening statement for the symposium.
- 好 - 还有 女士
- Sure. - Also, ma'am,
爱达荷州发生了灾难性的泥石流
catastrophic mudslides in Idaho.
州长要求联邦紧急状态
The governor is requesting a federal state of emergency.
- 这个应该在24小时内会消掉 - 好
- This should be cleared up in 24 hours. - Okay.
要避免皮肤在一段时间内接触到刺激性的东西
Just keep your skin free of all irritants for a few days.
- 女士 他说不要刺激性的 - 你就是个刺激物
- Ma'am, he said no irritants. - You're an irritant.
我们在爱达荷州输掉了多少?
How much did we lose Idaho by?
- 相当多 - 超过212,000票
- Shellacked. - Uh, well over 212,000 votes.
那我宣布进入去你妈逼的状态
Then I declare a state of go fuck yourself.
我才不要花钱把一堆脏路上的泥刮下来呢
I'm not spending money to scrape mud off a bunch of dirt roads.
- 你不是爱达荷州人吧 是吧 医生? - 不是 女士
- You're not from Idaho, are you, Doctor? - No, ma'am.
我不是有意听起来麻木不仁
I don't mean this to sound insensitive,
但你们不觉得泥石流
but don't you think that mudslides
是最好笑的自然灾害吗?
are the funniest kind of natural disasters?
我一直都很偏爱天坑 你知道的 哇
I've always been partial to sinkholes. You know, ah!
- 那些太好笑了 - 大自然的陷阱门
- Those are hilarious. - Nature's trapdoor.
女士 化妆品是刺激物但我们必须要用
Ma'am, makeup is an irritant and we really need that.
- 化妆品才不是刺激物呢 - 实际上是的 女士
- Makeup is not an irritant. - Actually, ma'am, yes, it is.
至少在48小时内要避免使用任何化妆品
Let's avoid any makeup on the facial area for at least 48 hours.
- 就一点点... – 噢 我不要这样
- You're gonna feel a small... - Oh, no, we're not gonna do this.
- 还是谢谢你的到来 – 那好 女士
- But thanks for coming. - Yes, ma'am.
我送你离开
I'll show you out.
我们需要看一下这个
We need to take a peek at this.
- 谢谢你 医生 – 要冷敷 盖瑞
- Thank you, Doc. - Cold compress, Gary.
随便啦
Whatever.
- 我的意思是... - 把我要说的话说出来了
- I mean... - Yeah, took the words right out of my mouth.
- 是吧 – 嗯
- Right? - Yeah.
- 女士? – 嗯?
- Ma'am? - Hmm?
本 今天韦斯格拉斯医生能到这儿吗?
Oh, Ben, were we able to get Dr. Weisglass here today?
- 当然了 女士 – 那好
- Absolutely, ma'am. - Okay.
太好了 凯瑟琳你在拍呢
Oh, good, Catherine. You're documenting this.
欢迎来到迈向新曙光的第一届年度...
Okay, welcome to the First Annual Towards a New Promise...
妈 别看镜头
Mom, don't look into the camera.
- 当我不在这 – 但你就在这啊
- Just pretend I'm not here. - But you are here.
是啊 可纪录片的精髓就在...
Yeah, but that's the point of a documentary film is that you're...
好吧 我一点都不懂
Okay, I don't understand
这些是什么鬼 懂不了
what this project is at all. I don't get it.
凯瑟琳 你发型怎么这样?
Catherine, why is that your hair?
他们准备好了 女士
They're ready for you, ma'am.
他来了
There he is.
- 韦斯格拉斯医生 - 很高兴再见到你 总统女士
- Dr. Weisglass. - Pleasure to see you again, Madam President.
真高兴你能赶来
I'm so pleased you were able to make it.
我很期待今天的谈话
And I'm really excited to start this conversation today.
- 好的 女士 - 山姆·奥克夫 我也是哈佛的
- Yes, ma'am. - Sam O'Keefe, also Harvard.
我知道今天我们要谈论的话题是艰难的
I think what we're gonna talk about today is hard,
但我觉得会是值得的 你觉得吗?
but I think it's going to be worth it, don't you agree?
- 我同意 是的 谢谢你 - 好 好
- I agree, yes. Thank you. - Good, good.
总统女士 伊莉莎·伯克
Madam President, Elisa Burke,
哈佛的非裔美国人研究的联合主席
cochair of African-American Studies at Howard.
- 伯克女士 是吗? - 是的
- Oh, Ms. Burke, is it? - Yes.
很好 每个艰难的对话
Great. Well, every difficult conversation
都是以一个句子开头的
starts with a sentence.
他妈的在搞什么? 为什么他们都是白人?
What the fuck is going on here? Why are they all white?
看起来像是曲棍球全明星周末
Looks like the NHL All-Star Weekend.
是啊 哈喽
Okay. Hello.
富兰克林·华盛顿 来自摩尔豪斯大学
Franklin Washington, Morehouse University.
摩尔豪斯大学
Now, Morehouse University
从历史上看是一个非裔美国人大学吧
is historically an African-American university.
- 从历史上看是 - 好
- Historically. - Okay.
我们需要赶紧找几个黑人来
We need to round up some blacks and fast.
- 我们需要找... – 别在广播上说 傻逼
- We need to round up... - Don't say it over the radio, asshole.
理查德! 太好了
Richard! Oh, thank God.
把苏找来 我们现在需要她
Go get Sue. We need her now.
- 现在就去 – 知道了
- Right now. - Yeah.
同志们 今天我放眼一看
Folks, I look around here today
就看到了像彩虹一样多彩的面孔
and I see a rainbow of faces, you know?
从非洲大草原来的面孔
Faces from the savannahs of Africa
到从英国城镇来的面孔
to the cities and towns of England.
从 从...从荷兰
Faces from... from Holland
甚至到应许是挪威的面孔
and even perhaps Norway.
把你打败的死死的 苏
In your fucking face, Sue.
我操!
Fuck!
大家保持冷静 当我们检查场地时
Everyone remain calm. We're in total lockdown
- 已经封锁好了 - 抓到她了
- while we search the premises. - We got her.
别动! 举起手来!
Freeze! Put your hands up!
哇哦 哇哦! 我在这儿工作
Whoa, whoa! I work here.
- 哈? 发生什么了? - 女士?
- Huh? What happened? - Ma'am?
麦克林托克先生 为什么在梅耶的白宫里
Mr. McLintock, why are there
那么少的有色人种?
so few people of color in the Meyer White House?
迈克 总统梅耶在乎黑人吗?
Mike, does President Meyer care about black people?
就在刚才 比尔·艾瑞克森
Just moments ago, Bill Ericsson,
前任白宫通讯主任
former Director of White House Communications,
在他卡洛拉马的家中被捕并且被联邦拘留了
was arrested at his Kalorama home and taken into federal custody.
由于罪行的严重性
Due to the seriousness of
不管谣言怎么说
the crimes and despite rumors to the contrary,
特赦没有公开进行
a pardon is not on the table.
遗憾的是 他对今天发生在种族研讨会上的混乱
Regrettably, he was also responsible for the chaos
任然负有责任
that occurred at the symposium on race today.
谢谢 到此为止
Thank you. That's all for now.
再度 我们今晚的头条
Once again, our top story tonight,
不光彩的总统助手比尔·艾瑞克森被联邦羁押
disgraced presidential aide Bill Ericsson goes into federal custody.
这是总统采取的强硬手段
This is a strong move by the president,
她也因此次糟糕透顶的种族研论会而饱受攻击
who was under fire for a disastrous symposium on race
这让人怀疑她
that left some wondering if
是否有能力管理她的行政部门
she had any control over her administration.
无可奉告!
No comment!
哇哦 他在电视上看起来好浮肿
Wow, he looks puffy on TV.
还好监狱会帮他健身的
Well, prison will get him in shape.
现在我要给你吹上
Okay, now I've just got to blow for,
差不多五分钟 好吗?
like, five minutes, all right?
不要走开 接下来会有华尔街疯狂的一天
When we come back, a wild day on Wall Street.
我们还将直播内华达州的情况
And we'll go live to Nevada where armies of staffers
在那里 军队人员以及梅耶和奥布莱恩阵营的志愿者们
and volunteers for the Meyer and O'Brien campaigns
正来到这片沙地里来监督和管理这次重新计票
are descending on the desert to monitor and manage the recount.
如果你们没有预约的话 这儿已经住满了
If you do not have a reservation, we are sold out.
没有多余的房间了
There are no more rooms at this hotel.
理查德 让你的人帮我们登记 我们去休息室吧
Richard, have your people check us in. We're going to the lounge.
乔纳 你来搞定
Jonah, take care of that.
克里夫也可以...
Cliff, would...
克里夫?
Cliff?
打扰一下 你在排队吗?
Excuse me, are you in line?
有谁知道队尾在哪儿吗?
Does anybody know where the line ends?